let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "I __________ working all afternoon and have just finished the assignment.",
    answer:"B had been",
    options:[
   
    "A have been",

    "B had been",
    
    "C shall be",
  
  
    "D am"
    ]
    },
  
    { 
    numb: 2,
    question:"Q2. Rohan __________ the movie before he read the review.",
    answer:"C had watched",
    options:[  
  
      "A watches",

      "B have watched",
    
      "C had watched",

      "D was watching"
      ]
    },
    
   
  
    {
    numb: 3,
    question:"Q3. He __________ in the States but he still does not have a command over the English language.",
    answer:"B has been living",
  
    options:[
      "A have been living",
  
      "B has been living",
      
      "C have lived",
      
      "D living"
    
    ]
    },
        
   
  
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Q4. By the next month, we shall __________ the project.",
    answer:"D have completed",
    options: [
      "A has completed",
        
      "B completing",
        
      "C completed",
        
      "D have completed"
      ]
    },
   
  
   {
   numb: 5,
   question: "Q5. Every boy and girl __________ in the class today.",
   answer:"B is present",
    options:
    ["A are present",
    
    "B is present",
    
    "C have present",
    
    "D had present"
    ]
    },

    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which type of sentence must end with a question mark?",
        answer:"interrogative",
        options:[
          "interrogative",
          "imperative",
         "exclamative",
         "assertive"]
        },
     { 
      numb: 7,

      question:"A sentence that's used to give someone an order or a command is an _______ sentence.",
      answer:"imperative",
      options:
       [ 
        "assertive",
        "interrogative",
        "imperative",
        "exclamative"
      ]
      },
    {  
      numb:8,
      question:"The function of a declarative sentence is to _______ someone about something.",
      answer:"tell",
      options:[
       "ask",
        "tell",
       "surprise",
       "shoked"
      ]
    },

     {
      numb:9,
   
        question:"What does an exclamative sentence usually end with?",
        answer:"an exclamation mark",
        options:[
          "a full-stop or period",
          "a question mark",
          "an exclamation mark",
          "a colon"

      ]
    },
     {
       numb:10,
       question:"Sit down and be quiet! What type of sentence is this?",
       answer:"imperative",
       options:
        [
         " exclamative",
          "imperative",
          "interrogative",
          "assertive"
        ]
      },
      {
        numb:11,
        question:"Have you met Fatima? She is a friend of ---------- ?",
        answer:"my mothers",
        options:[

        "my",
        "my mother",
        "my mothers",
        "me"
        ]
      },
      {
          numb:12,

        question:"Synonym of reformation is ------- ?",
        answer:"change",
        options:[
        "repetition",
        "change",
        "revelation",
        "retreat"
        ]



      },
    {
        numb:13,
        question:"I am astonished ----- his behaviour ?",
        answer:"with",
        options:[
        "To",
        "From",
        "With",
        "On"
        ]




    },
    {
        numb:14,
        question:"Identify the following groups of words as fragment, independent clause, or dependent  clause. the picnic being planned for some time now  ",
        answer:"Dependent clause",
        options:[
        "Fragment",
        "Independent clause",
        "Dependent clause",
        "Subordinate clause"
      ]
    },
    {
        numb:15,
        question:"South Africa brushed ----------- the threat of tougher economic sanctions ?",
        answer:"off",
        options:[
        "of",
        "off",
        "down",
        "about"
        ]
    }
    ]


    